<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--This file was created with ExeOutput 24.2.0.0. Please respect the structure of the XML file if you want to import changes back to ExeOutput.--><hescript name="UserMain" desc="Lets you insert commands in global events.">
	<contents><![CDATA[// UserMain
// This script contains special functions related to some of the events triggered by the application.
// You can then optionally add new commands.

function OnBeforeNavigate(NewURL, TargetFrame: String): Boolean;
begin
 // Before the application displays a page. Set Result to True to stop the operation.
 Result := False;
end;

procedure OnPHPErrorMessage(ErrorMsg: String);
begin
 // When an error is returned by the PHP runtime.
end;

function OnRouterURL(RequestedURL, RequestedFilename, PathInfo, QueryString: String): String;
begin
// Lets you reroute any URL.
// Set Result to an empty string for no redirection.
// Set Result to the new URL if you want a permanent redirection.
 Result := "";
end;

procedure OnNavigateComplete(URL: String);
begin
 // When a page has been displayed.
end;

function OnPubLoaded: Boolean;
begin
 // When the application is starting.
 // Set Result to True if you want to exit immediately without any warning.
 Result := False;
end;

procedure OnPubBeingClosed;
begin
 // When the application is going to be closed.
end;

procedure OnDisplayWindow(WindowName: String);
begin
 // When a window is going to be displayed (including main and secondary windows).
end;

procedure OnStartMainWindow;
begin
 // When the main window is going to be displayed (just before the homepage is shown).
end;

procedure OnCloseWindow(WindowName: String);
begin
 // When a window is closed by the user.
end;

function OnTimer(TimerName: String): Boolean;
begin
 // Occurs when a specified amount of time, determined by StartTimer HEScript function, has passed.
 // Note: use StopTimer to disable the timer or set Result to True.
 Result := False;
end;

function OnInvalidPasswordAtStartup: Boolean;
begin
 // Occurs when an invalid global password is provided.
 // Note: set to True if you want the application NOT to display an error message and exit.
 Result := False;
end;

function OnExpiredPublication: Boolean;
begin
 // Occurs when the global expiration date is reached.
 // Note: set to True if you want the application NOT to display an error message and exit.
 Result := False;
end;

procedure OnTrayIconClick;
begin
 // The user clicks on the tray icon.
end;

procedure OnTrayIconDblClick;
begin
 // The user double-clicks on the tray icon.
end;

procedure OnPrintPage;
begin
 // When a user wants to print the current page.
end;]]></contents>
</hescript>
